<root><blog><title>Sri Lanka: Google Map On Flood Affected Areas · Global Voices</title><content>Sri Lanka: Google Map On Flood Affected Areas · Global Voices GlobalVoices in Learn more » Global Voices in English English The world is talking, are you listening? The world is talking, are you listening? About Get Involved Press nextdir Contact Donate Subscribe Global Voices is an international community of bloggers who report on blogs and citizen media from around the world. Learn why » Search Countries Topics Contributors Sri Lanka: Google Map On Flood Affected Areas Posted 13 January 2011 Written byRezwan Countries Sri Lanka Topics Breaking News, Disaster, Relief  Rescue Languages English Sri Lanka Groundviews publishes a frequently updated Google Map which identifies the main flood-affected regions in Sri Lanka, sites where relief and rescue operations have been conducted and other information. Tweet reddit StumbleUpon delicious Instapaper More stories about Sri Lanka South Asia: Looking Back at the Citizen Media Storylines in 2010 South Asia: The Morality Of Exposing Others Secrets South Asia: Bloggers on ‘Burn a Quran Day More » Cancel this reply Start the conversation Authors, please log in » Name (required) Email (will not be published) (required) Website Subscribe to comments on this post via email Guidelines All comments are reviewed by a moderator. Do not submit your comment more than once or it may be identified as spam. Please treat others with respect. Comments containing hate speech, obscenity, and personal attacks will not be approved. Happy New Year from Global Voices! Global Voices is a super-important part in fixing what I call the caring problem. Joi Ito, Japan Donate now » More stories about South Asia Bangladesh, India: Human Rights Hanging On The Border Fence Bangladesh: Stock Market Plunge Hurts Small Investors Bhutan: Criminalizing The Use Of Tobacco Stirs Outrage Pakistan: Salman Taseers Tragic Assassination And The Blasphemy Law More » Updates about South Asia 12 January 2011 India Reading Cafe reacts on the news that the Indian government is seriously considering asking Google to help it in monitoring emails. • Rezwan Pakistan Sana Saleem proposes a public discourse between the activists and clerics to resolve the current crisis in Pakistan with a mutual consensus. • Rezwan India Shital Shah at Think Change India talks about a free mobile application for NGOs that enables field staffs to collect data using their existing mobile phones and transfer it on a real-time basis. • Rezwan Nepal Ujjwal Acharya questions the newly introduced practice of two dailies of Nepal - Kantipur and The Kathmandu Post - where readers can send their feedback on opinion pieces and editorial via SMS. • Rezwan Sri Lanka Sarvodaya blog highlights the relief efforts targeted towards the flood victims in Ampara and Batticaloa districts of Sri Lanka. • Rezwan Featured project Cablegate: Lessons on tech for transparency Wikileaks release of over 250,000 United States embassy cables is one of the hottest subjects in media and government right now. Renata Av... More » Learn about all our projects Some of our funders Learn more » Recent comments China: Comments on Ai Weiweis River Crab Banquet Andy, please read Caijins 11/17 story on the studio demolition titled ?????????-????? for what really... More » Haiti: One Year Ago...We Remember I just heard the tail end of an interview with 2 persons who are working... More » Lebanon: Eleven Cabinet Members Resign, Toppling Government It is very true that Lebanon can operate without government. And the people are used... More » Monthly archives Monthly archives January 2011   ·   315 posts December 2010   ·   806 posts November 2010   ·   734 posts October 2010   ·   810 posts September 2010   ·   782 posts August 2010   ·   818 posts July 2010   ·   900 posts June 2010   ·   753 posts May 2010   ·   721 posts April 2010   ·   605 posts March 2010   ·   730 posts February 2010   ·   621 posts January 2010   ·   700 posts December 2009   ·   681 posts November 2009   ·   740 posts October 2009   ·   664 posts September 2009   ·   706 posts August 2009   ·   747 posts July 2009   ·   889 posts June 2009   ·   793 posts May 2009   ·   769 posts April 2009   ·   915 posts March 2009   ·   1052 posts February 2009   ·   967 posts January 2009   ·   1134 posts December 2008   ·   1023 posts November 2008   ·   932 posts October 2008   ·   942 posts September 2008   ·   1021 posts August 2008   ·   1280 posts July 2008   ·   1169 posts June 2008   ·   941 posts May 2008   ·   1268 posts April 2008   ·   1366 posts March 2008   ·   1209 posts February 2008   ·   1170 posts January 2008   ·   1386 posts December 2007   ·   1242 posts November 2007   ·   1445 posts October 2007   ·   1169 posts September 2007   ·   1022 posts August 2007   ·   1367 posts July 2007   ·   1236 posts June 2007   ·   1241 posts May 2007   ·   1481 posts April 2007   ·   1259 posts March 2007   ·   1267 posts February 2007   ·   1122 posts January 2007   ·   1116 posts December 2006   ·   905 posts November 2006   ·   1139 posts October 2006   ·   1121 posts September 2006   ·   1002 posts August 2006   ·   1096 posts July 2006   ·   1062 posts June 2006   ·   1234 posts May 2006   ·   1379 posts April 2006   ·   1203 posts March 2006   ·   1231 posts February 2006   ·   1063 posts January 2006   ·   1014 posts December 2005   ·   730 posts November 2005   ·   904 posts October 2005   ·   846 posts September 2005   ·   765 posts August 2005   ·   841 posts July 2005   ·   538 posts June 2005   ·   63 posts May 2005   ·   46 posts April 2005   ·   29 posts March 2005   ·   30 posts February 2005   ·   5 posts January 2005   ·   15 posts December 2004   ·   22 posts November 2004   ·   5 posts October 2004   ·   2 posts See what happened at our last Summit! You love us right? nextdir Contributors View all contributors » Navigation About Get Involved Press nextdir Contact Donate Subscribe Creative Commons This site is licensed as Creative Commons Attribution 3.0. Please read our attribution policy to learn about freely redistributing our work. Search Funders Learn more » Translations of this site Learn more » World regions Americas  Central Asia  Caucasus  East Asia  Eastern  Central Europe  Middle East  North Africa  Oceania  South Asia  Sub-Saharan Africa  Western Europe  Countries Afghanistan  Albania  Algeria  American Samoa  Angola  Anguilla  Antigua and Barbuda  Argentina  Armenia  Aruba  Australia  Austria  Azerbaijan  Bahamas  Bahrain  Bangladesh  Barbados  Belarus  Belgium  Belize  Benin  Bermuda  Bhutan  Bolivia  Bonaire  Bosnia Herzegovina  Botswana  Brazil  British Virgin Islands  Brunei  Bulgaria  Burkina Faso  Burundi  Cambodia  Cameroon  Canada  Cape Verde  Cayman Islands  Central African Republic  Chad  Chile  China  Colombia  Comoros  Cook Islands  Costa Rica  Cote dIvoire  Croatia  Cuba  Curaçao  Cyprus  Czech Republic  D.R. of Congo  Denmark  Djibouti  Dominica  Dominican Republic  East Timor  Ecuador  Egypt  El Salvador  Equatorial Guinea  Eritrea  Estonia  Ethiopia  Fiji  Finland  France  French Guiana  Gabon  Gambia  Georgia  Germany  Ghana  Greece  Grenada  Guadeloupe  Guatemala  Guinea  Guinea-Bissau  Guyana  Haiti  Honduras  Hong Kong (China)  Hungary  Iceland  India  Indonesia  Iran  Iraq  Ireland  Israel  Italy  Jamaica  Japan  Jordan  Kazakhstan  Kenya  Kosovo  Kuwait  Kyrgyzstan  Laos  Latvia  Lebanon  Lesotho  Liberia  Libya  Lithuania  Luxembourg  Macau (China)  Macedonia  Madagascar  Malawi  Malaysia  Maldives  Mali  Malta  Martinique  Mauritania  Mauritius  Mayotte  Mexico  Moldova  Monaco  Mongolia  Montenegro  Montserrat  Morocco  Mozambique  Myanmar (Burma)  Namibia  Nepal  Netherlands  New Caledonia  New Zealand  Nicaragua  Niger  Nigeria  North Korea  Norway  Oman  Pakistan  Palestine  Panama  Papua New Guinea  Paraguay  Peru  Philippines  Poland  Portugal  Puerto Rico (U.S.)  Qatar  Republic of Congo  Reunion  Romania  Russia  Rwanda  Saint Helena  Saint Lucia  Samoa  San Marino  Sao Tome and Principe  Saudi Arabia  Senegal  Serbia  Seychelles  Sierra Leone  Singapore  Slovakia  Slovenia  Somalia  Somaliland  South Africa  South Korea  Spain  Sri Lanka  St. Barthélémy  St. Eustatius  St. Maarten  St. Vincent  the Grenadines  St.Kitts  Nevis  Sudan  Suriname  Swaziland  Sweden  Switzerland  Syria  Tahiti  Taiwan (ROC)  Tajikistan  Tanzania  Thailand  Togo  Tonga  Trinidad  Tobago  Tunisia  Turkey  Turkmenistan  Turks  Caicos Isl.  U.S.A.  US Virgin Islands  Uganda  Ukraine  United Arab Emirates  United Kingdom  Uruguay  Uzbekistan  Vatican City  Venezuela  Vietnam  Wallis  Futuna  Western Sahara  Yemen  Zambia  Zimbabwe  Based on the Wikipedia list of countries, details. Languages Afrikaans  Arabic  Armenian  Azerbaijani  Bahasa  Bangla  Belarusian  Bosnian  Bulgarian  Burmese  Chinese  Croatian  Danish  Dutch  English  Farsi  Filipino  French  French Creoles  Georgian  German  Greek  Hebrew  Hindi  Hungarian  Italian  Japanese  Kannada  Kazakh  Khmer  Korean  Latvian  Lingala  Macedonian  Malagasy  Nepali  Polish  Portuguese  Romanian  Russian  Serbian  Slovak  Slovenian  Spanish  Swahili  Tajik  Tamil  Tetum  Thai  Tibetan  Turkish  Ukrainian  Urdu  Uzbek  Vietnamese  Agriculture  Arts  Culture  Breaking News  Business  Children  Cyber-Activism  Development  Diaspora  Disaster  Economics  Education  Elections  Energy  Entertainment  Environment  Ethnicity  Film  Finance  Food  Freedom of Speech  Gender  Governance  Health  History  Human Rights  Humanitarian  Humor  Ideas  Indigenous  Industry  International Relations  Internet  Telecoms  LGBT  Labor  Language  Law  Literature  Media  Music  Photography  Politics  Protest  Racism  Refugees  Relief  Rescue  Religion  Science  Software  Tools  Sport  Technology  Travel  War  Conflict  Youth  Special topics About GVO  Announcements  Blogger News  Blogger Profiles  Books  CSR  Conversations for a Better World  GV Contributor Profiles  GV05 Summit  GVDelhi2006  Human Rights Video  Olympics  Organizations  Participant news  Projects  Resources  RuNet Echo  Technology for Transparency Network  The Future of ICT for Development  Tools  United Nations  Posts with Photos Video J. Nambiza Tungaraza26 posts Jorge Gobbi46 posts Stephen Cairns9 posts Lynn Palermo4 posts Paula Odhiambo5 posts Asteris Masouras13 posts Jennifer Cheung7 posts Catherine Lewis1 posts Silvia Viñas419 posts Layal Al Khatib29 posts Suzanne Lehn41 posts Alexey Sidorenko286 posts View all contributors »</content></blog></root>