<root><blog><title>Hicham Aaboubou Back With Impact</title><content>Hicham Aaboubou Back With Impact Home About Archives Soccer Bodies CSA CSL FIFA MLS NotSoccer Aggregators Blogs  Things Fight Songs Loop 48 Properties Tunes Online Nukes Are You Ready Aren’t Nukes Swell Atomic Kitten Atomik Harmonik B52s Blondie Atomic Bomba Atomica Daisy Girl Day After Yackety Sax Duck And Cover Song Fortunate Son I Called NNS Jolity Farm KaBoom Myra Breckinridge Nagasaki Now Then Dimitri Protection In The Nuclear Age Survival Under Attack Twenty Fifty Three We Will All Go Together We’ll Meet Again WEBMedia Log in Close Remember me Lost your password? Beautiful Game Grassroots MLS Recaps News  Scores Top Stories Features Almanac Asides It’s Called Football OSAtv Rednationtv Soccer In Toronto Farrago Music Box Scribes Subscribe via RSS Feed Canada Men NT Canada Women NT Impact Toronto FC Whitecaps Recently Posted Hicham Aaboubou Back With Impact U23s Off To Arizona Is Darlington Nagbe Ready For Whitecaps Underpaid Adrain And Nana Talks Head South OSAtv: With OSA President Ron Smale CSA Reform The Ontario Way Nicolas Lindsay Suffers Knee Injury Ottawa Fury Opt For Steve Payne Whitecaps Pick First In MLS Superdraft Who Is Andrzej Ornoch? MLS Good Name Good Logo Hi-Lo The Alberta Situation De Guzman’s Chance At Redemption Klinsmann Tempers Optimism 1974 All Over Again Popular Topics ben.knight concacaf csa csl impact laffs listener.girly listener.pop listener.rock mls mnt olympics rocket.robin tfc tourney video whitecaps wleague wnt world cup Nukester’s Videos Music by The Real Tuesday Weld - Kix Music by Eminem - Felony Franks Rap Music by Steve Earle - Galway Girl Words by GROUCHO - I dont know what they have to say. It makes no difference anyway. Whatever it is, Im AGAINST IT. Music by The Thornlie Boys - Rangers Till I Die Nukesters Theme Song Nukesters Official Chowdown Nukesters Girly Tribute Nukesters Our Say, Our Way Nukesters Soccer Song News  Scores|January 13, 2011 5:54 pm Hicham Aaboubou Back With Impact MONTREAL – The Montreal Impact announced Thursday that central defender Hicham Aaboubou has agreed to a new one-year deal with the club. Aaboubou, a 31-year-old Canadian resident and native of Morocco, will play his fourth season with the Impact in 2011. After playing just 17 matches in 2007 and 2009, Aaboubou solidified his spot on the team’s defensive line last season. In 2010, he played 24 regular season matches, all as a starter (2,123 minutes), reaching the 2,000-minute mark for the first time in his career with Montreal. He also played the full 90 minutes in four playoff matches and two Nutrilite Canadian Championship matches. “After the season he had last year, Hicham deserved to be back in 2011,” declared Impact technical director Nick De Santis. “When Cédric Joqueviel and Stefano Pesoli left the team during the season, he played a very important role. Hicham demonstrated a high level of professionalism and has always been loyal to our club.” “We will have experience at central defense with the return of Nevio (Pizzolitto) and Hicham, which is important at that position,” added De Santis. “With the addition of a young central defender, we would be in excellent shape at that spot in 2011.” “Being a Montrealer, I’m very happy to be staying with the Impact for another season,” said Aaboubou. “I think I proved myself in 2010 and showed everyone that I have my place on this team. My objective is to have another good season in 2011 and prove that I can follow the team into MLS, but I’m not looking to skip any steps. What I want is to win championships this coming season.” Team captain Nevio Pizzolitto accepted a one-year deal for 2011 on January 5. The Impact now has a total of 13 players under contract for this season, the club’s final campaign in second division. FIRST MATCH FOR U21 ACADEMY The Impact’s Under-21 Academy will play the first exhibition match of its training camp this Sunday at 4pm versus the University of Quebec at Trois-Rivières (UQTR) at the Alphonse Desjardins Sports Centre. The U21 Academy, which starts its camp on January 3, expects to play a total of 14 pre-season matches. Managed by head coach Philippe Eullaffroy, the club is preparing for its second season in the Canadian Soccer League, which kicks off in May. Tags: impact Share this post: Leave a Reply Click here to cancel reply.   Haeremai Blow It Up Good, Real Good » Pick a suitable weapon and press Nuke It! © Copyright 2011 — Nuke Soccer. All Rights Reserved Designed by</content></blog></root>