<root><blog><title>Annies Ushers in 2011 Year of the Rabbit With New Product Offerings; Deeper Commitment to Connecting Families With Real Food | SYS-CON MEDIA</title><content>Annies Ushers in 2011 Year of the Rabbit With New Product Offerings; Deeper Commitment to Connecting Families With Real Food | SYS-CON MEDIA   Jump to a SYS-CON Magazine .NET Developers Journal apache.SYS-CON.com AjaxWorld Magazine - AWM Cloud Computing Journal cms.SYS-CON.com ColdFusion Developers Journal crm.SYS-CON.com Eclipse Developers Journal Enterprise Open Source Magazine Flex Developers Journal - Flex HP.SYS-CON.com Internet Video - iTV iPhone Developers Journal - iPHONE IT Solutions Guide Java Developers Journal Linux.SYS-CON.com Open Web Developers Journal oracle.SYS-CON.com perl.SYS-CON.com PHP.SYS-CON.com PowerBuilder Developers Journal python.SYS-CON.com redhat.SYS-CON.com ruby.SYS-CON.com SEO/SEM (Search) Journal Silverlight Developers Journal saas.SYS-CON.com SAP.SYS-CON.com SOAWorld Magazine - SWM Symbian Developers Journal Virtualization.SYS-CON.com Web 2.0 Journal WebLogic Journal WebSphere Journal Wireless Business  Technology XML Journal The i-Technology Media! Register | Log in       .NET  ·  AJAX  ·  CLOUD  ·  ECLIPSE  ·  FLEX  ·  OPEN WEB  ·  iPHONE  ·  JAVA  ·  LINUX  ·  OPEN SOURCE  ·  ORACLE  ·  PBDJ  ·  SEARCH  ·  SILVERLIGHT  ·  SOA  ·  VIRTUALIZATION  ·  WEB 2.0  ·  WIRELESS  ·  XML Comments Web 2.0 Is Dead. Long Live Web 2.0! By Fuat Kircaali rabcraig wrote: I regret what i said, i dont think that Craigslist has to improve, theyre really simplistic and you can search classifieds like you would do in a newspaper. Dec. 29, 2010 06:59 PM EST read more  respond » Cloud Expo on Google News  Did you read todays front page stories  breaking news?  Cloud Expo  Virtualization 2010 West DIAMOND SPONSOR: Oracle Roadmap to Enterprise Cloud Computing PLATINUM PLUS SPONSORS: Abiquo Next Generation Cloud Management - Introducing the Virtual Enterprise Adaptivity The Enterprise Cloud Lifecycle Microsoft The Move is On: Cloud Strategies for Businesses PLATINUM SPONSORS: Red Hat Unlocking the Value of the Cloud Today SAP The Journey to On Demand - Lessons Learned from Small, High-Growth Customers Unisys What if You Could Transform IT Your Way, Using Cloud 2.0? GOLD SPONSORS: CA Technologies. Changing the Game: How to Get a Cloud Service Up and Running in Less Than 30 Days Cisco Cisco Cloud Strategy, Within and Across Data Centers Compuware Borderless Applications: The Future of Performance in the Cloud Cordys The Business Value of the Cloud Intel Next Cloud on the Horizon: Exascale to Microservers Navisite Cloud Computing – Extending Your IT Infrastructure Quest Software The Private Cloud in Practice: Case Studies  Proven Strategies Rackspace Hosting OpenStack for the Enterprise SoftLayer Its All Cloud: Blurring the Line Between Dedicated and Cloud Service Terremark Parting the Clouds - Evaluating Clouds and Cloud Providers for the Enterprise VMware An Evolutionary Path to Cloud Computing - VMwares Private, Public, and Hybrid Cloud Solutions Click For 2009 West Event Webcasts  Cloud Expo  Virtualization 2010 East PLATINUM PLUS SPONSORS: Abiquo Eliminate Vendor Lock-in with Next-Generation Virtualization Management Adaptivity Building the Cloud Blueprint for Enterprise IT GOLD SPONSORS: Cordys Continuous Business Transformation: The Cloud Value Chain Microsoft Microsofts Cloud Services Approach Navisite Defining Enterprise-Class Cloud Computing: Managed Cloud Services Surgient Deploy an Enterprise Private Cloud in Less Than 30 Days with Surgient Terremark Parting the Clouds - Evaluating Clouds and Cloud Providers for the Enterprise The Planet The Cloud’s Not the Revolution: Cloud Usage Is Unisys Storm Clouds - Disruptive Technologies Creating the New Normal Virtual Ark Third-Generation Outsourcing Is Here! Click For 2009 West Event Webcasts  Live Google News by SYS-CON! Top Three Links You Must Click On From the Wires Annies Ushers in 2011 Year of the Rabbit With New Product Offerings; Deeper Commitment to Connecting Families With Real Food 2010 milestones included 25% increase in sales, six new product introductions and Root 4 Kids initiative to encourage kids to eat more real food By: PR Newswire Jan. 13, 2011 05:04 PM NAPA, Calif., Jan. 13, 2011 /PRNewswire/ -- Good news for Bernie, Annies mascot and Rabbit of Approval, and consumers nationwide: February 3, 2011 officially marks the start of Year of the Rabbit. According to the Chinese Zodiac, the Year of the Rabbit signifies a year of calm, thoughtfulness, giving and persistence. Annies, the leading provider of natural and organic pasta meals, snacks, salad dressings and condiments, will embrace these traits as it kicks off a new year filled with product launches, ingredient improvements, initiatives that connect families with real food, and a move to new corporate headquarters. As Annies moves into the Year of the Rabbit, were thinking about how we can continue nourishing busy families who crave convenient, delicious food made with real ingredients, said John Foraker, Annies CEO. We are energized by continually evolving our company to meet the needs of our consumers. We constantly push ourselves to improve our products, programs and positive impact on our world, and look forward to reaching even more families in 2011. Year of the Rabbit: New Product Introductions, Innovations Annies will expand its snack and pasta offerings and enter new product categories in 2011. Among the first of these introductions is a new line of Organic Granola Bars in three delicious flavors - Peanutty, Chocolate Chipper and Berry Berry - hitting store shelves nationwide in January. Kid-friendly Organic Pretzel Bunnies in Original, Honey Wheat and Spelt varieties, also debut early this winter. Next, new Gingersnap and SnickerDoodle Gluten Free Bunny Cookies, available in February, offer a sweet treat for those following gluten-free diets. In addition to new product offerings, Annies continually strives to enhance the quality of existing offerings. Some specific changes in the Year of the Rabbit include: Sodium Reduction: Annies continues to lower the bar on sodium and will reduce sodium in its products by another 15% over the next five years. More than 85% of Annies products already meet the sodium guidelines established by the National Salt Reduction Initiative without making any formula changes. rBST-Free Milk Ingredients: Annies organic products have always been free of synthetic hormones, and the company has always been committed to sourcing as much all-natural, rBST-free milk as possible. In 2011, Annies will be able to source all milk ingredients from cows not treated with synthetic growth hormones. Cocoa: Annies has reformulated its chocolate cookies and cereal to use a cocoa that gives the chocolate products more of a mild, milk chocolate color and flavor. More Organic Products: In 1998, Annies became the first brand to offer organic mac  cheese; the company continues to increase its offerings of organic products. In 2010, 87% of Annies products were made with organic ingredients, and Annies has more than doubled the number of products it makes with organic ingredients over the past five years. Annies is committed to continued growth of organic ingredients to reduce the amount of synthetic fertilizers and pesticides in the food supply and minimize the exposure of farmers and their families to these harmful chemicals. Year of the Rabbit: Real Food Initiatives Annies is dedicated to supporting organic farmers across the country through use of organic ingredients. Over the past five years, Annies has used more than 71 million pounds of organic ingredients. In 2010, Annies organic wheat purchases alone equated to the average yield of approximately 11,000 acres of organic wheat. Organic farming helps to build healthy soils, clean waterways, increase drought and flood resistance and conserve biodiversity. To support the next generation of organic farmers, Annies will award $75,000 in Sustainable Agriculture Scholarship funds in 2011. Since the scholarship program was founded in 2000, Annies has contributed more than $300,000 in scholarships to students studying organic agriculture and environmental sciences. In 2011, Annies will also further its work connecting kids directly with real food. Root 4 Kids, a new cause-related initiative, aims to inspire 1 million kids nationwide to dig and plant new vegetables. Launched in September 2010, more than 70,000 families have joined the movement to date, helping to foster a new generation of veggie-loving kids. Additionally, 150 school gardens will receive funding this year through Annies Grants for Gardens program, allowing more kids direct access to lessons about real food. Year of the Rabbit: Growing Sustainably Annies business remains strong, with annual sales up 15% over each of the past five years, and a 25% increase in 2010. To support continued company growth, Annies is relocating its corporate headquarters to Berkeley in spring 2011. The space is being built out to meet LEED certification standards and will feature reclaimed furniture, natural light and eco-friendly finishes throughout. In addition, a parking lot will be turned into a green space with organic garden beds. About Annies Homegrown Annies Homegrown offers delicious, all-natural and organic alternatives to traditional comfort foods and snacks. Since Annie Withey created her first box of mac  cheese in 1989, Annies has been dedicated to delivering great-tasting, easy-to-prepare products that are healthy for people and the planet. Today the portfolio includes pasta meals, crackers, grahams, cereals and fruit snacks made with straight-from-nature ingredients. Annies products are available nationwide at major grocery stores, natural food stores, mass retailers and club stores. For more information, visit www.Annies.com. Annies is also on Facebook (www.Facebook.com/annieshomegrown) and Twitter (@annieshomegrown). SOURCE Annies, Inc. Published Jan. 13, 2011 Copyright © 2011 SYS-CON Media, Inc. — All Rights Reserved. Syndicated stories and blog feeds, all rights reserved by the author. About PR Newswire Copyright © 2007 PR Newswire. All rights reserved. Republication or redistribution of PRNewswire content is expressly prohibited without the prior written consent of PRNewswire. PRNewswire shall not be liable for any errors or delays in the content, or for any actions taken in reliance thereon. Subscribe to the Worlds Most Powerful Newsletters Subscribe to Our Rss Feeds  Get Your SYS-CON News Live! Click to Add our RSS Feeds to the Service of Your Choice: View Additional SYS-CON Feeds Publish Your Article! Please send it to editorial(at)sys-con.com! Advertise on this site! Contact advertising(at)sys-con.com! 201 802-3021  SYS-CON Featured Whitepapers ADS BY GOOGLE  Breaking Java News ATW Gold Corp.: Name Change to Redhill Resources Corp. OnStar Looking for Application Developers of the Future C7 Technologies and Dalcon Communication Systems, Inc. Announce Partnership TeamStaff, Inc. Announces Delay of Year End Results Billionaire Alki David and Mike Mozart Release Second Incendiary CBS Video in Response to Leslie Moonves Comments American Capital Agency Corp. Announces Pricing of Public Offering of Common Stock The X-Change Corporation Completes the 2010 Audit and Files a 10k to Complete the Asset Purchase of 21-Century Silicon, Inc. LSSOs Legal Lean Sigma(TM) Process Improvement Certifications Help Legal Profession Increase Efficiency, Deliver Value and Boost Profits Seattle Lighting Receives First Batch of VU1 ESL Energy Efficient Light Bulbs INOVA Announces Sale to One of the Largest Operating Crews in Southern Iraq  ADVERTISE   |   MAGAZINE SUBSCRIPTIONS   |   FREE BREAKING-NEWSLETTERS!   |   SYS-CON.TV   |   BLOG-N-PLAY!   |   WEBCAST   |   EDUCATION   |   RESEARCH .NET Developers Journal - .NETDJ   |   ColdFusion Developers Journal - CFDJ   |   Eclipse Developers Journal - EDJ   |   Enterprise Open Source Magazine - EOS Open Web Developers Journal - OPENWEB   |   iPhone Developers Journal - iPHONE   |   Virtualization - Virtualization   |   Java Developers Journal - JDJ   |   Linux.SYS-CON.com PowerBuilder Developers Journal - PBDJ   |   SEO / SEM Journal - SJ   |   SOAWorld Magazine - SOAWM   |   IT Solutions Guide - ITSG   |   Symbian Developers Journal - SDJ WebLogic Developers Journal - WLDJ   |   WebSphere Journal - WJ   |   Wireless Business  Technology - WBT   |   XML-Journal - XMLJ   |   Internet Video - iTV Flex Developers Journal - Flex   |   AJAXWorld Magazine - AWM   |   Silverlight Developers Journal - SLDJ   |   PHP.SYS-CON.com   |   Web 2.0 Journal - WEB2 Apache   |   CMS   |   CRM   |   HP   |   Oracle Journal   |   Perl   |   Python   |   Red Hat   |   Ruby on Rails   |   SAP   |   SaaS SYS-CON MEDIA:   ABOUT US   |   CONTACT US   |   COMPANY NEWS   |   CAREERS   |   SITE MAP SYS-CON EVENTS:   |  AJAXWorld Conference  Expo  |  iPhone Developer Summit  |  Cloud Computing Conference  Expo  |  SOA World Conference  Expo  |  Virtualization Conference  Expo INTERNATIONAL SITES:   India  |  U.K.  |  Canada  |  Germany  |  France  |  Australia  |  Italy  |  Spain  |  Netherlands  |  Brazil  |  Belgium  Terms of Use  Our Privacy Statement     About Newsfeeds / Video Feeds Copyright ©1994-2008 SYS-CON Publications, Inc. All Rights Reserved. All marks are trademarks of SYS-CON Media. Reproduction in whole or in part in any form or medium without express written permission of SYS-CON Publications, Inc. is prohibited.    close this window</content></blog></root>