<root><blog><title>Western Titanium Resolves Pending Charges | SYS-CON MEDIA</title><content>Western Titanium Resolves Pending Charges | SYS-CON MEDIA   Jump to a SYS-CON Magazine .NET Developers Journal apache.SYS-CON.com AjaxWorld Magazine - AWM Cloud Computing Journal cms.SYS-CON.com ColdFusion Developers Journal crm.SYS-CON.com Eclipse Developers Journal Enterprise Open Source Magazine Flex Developers Journal - Flex HP.SYS-CON.com Internet Video - iTV iPhone Developers Journal - iPHONE IT Solutions Guide Java Developers Journal Linux.SYS-CON.com Open Web Developers Journal oracle.SYS-CON.com perl.SYS-CON.com PHP.SYS-CON.com PowerBuilder Developers Journal python.SYS-CON.com redhat.SYS-CON.com ruby.SYS-CON.com SEO/SEM (Search) Journal Silverlight Developers Journal saas.SYS-CON.com SAP.SYS-CON.com SOAWorld Magazine - SWM Symbian Developers Journal Virtualization.SYS-CON.com Web 2.0 Journal WebLogic Journal WebSphere Journal Wireless Business  Technology XML Journal The i-Technology Media! Register | Log in       .NET  ·  AJAX  ·  CLOUD  ·  ECLIPSE  ·  FLEX  ·  OPEN WEB  ·  iPHONE  ·  JAVA  ·  LINUX  ·  OPEN SOURCE  ·  ORACLE  ·  PBDJ  ·  SEARCH  ·  SILVERLIGHT  ·  SOA  ·  VIRTUALIZATION  ·  WEB 2.0  ·  WIRELESS  ·  XML Comments Web 2.0 Is Dead. Long Live Web 2.0! By Fuat Kircaali rabcraig wrote: I regret what i said, i dont think that Craigslist has to improve, theyre really simplistic and you can search classifieds like you would do in a newspaper. Dec. 29, 2010 06:59 PM EST read more  respond » Cloud Expo on Google News  Did you read todays front page stories  breaking news?  Cloud Expo  Virtualization 2010 West DIAMOND SPONSOR: Oracle Roadmap to Enterprise Cloud Computing PLATINUM PLUS SPONSORS: Abiquo Next Generation Cloud Management - Introducing the Virtual Enterprise Adaptivity The Enterprise Cloud Lifecycle Microsoft The Move is On: Cloud Strategies for Businesses PLATINUM SPONSORS: Red Hat Unlocking the Value of the Cloud Today SAP The Journey to On Demand - Lessons Learned from Small, High-Growth Customers Unisys What if You Could Transform IT Your Way, Using Cloud 2.0? GOLD SPONSORS: CA Technologies. Changing the Game: How to Get a Cloud Service Up and Running in Less Than 30 Days Cisco Cisco Cloud Strategy, Within and Across Data Centers Compuware Borderless Applications: The Future of Performance in the Cloud Cordys The Business Value of the Cloud Intel Next Cloud on the Horizon: Exascale to Microservers Navisite Cloud Computing – Extending Your IT Infrastructure Quest Software The Private Cloud in Practice: Case Studies  Proven Strategies Rackspace Hosting OpenStack for the Enterprise SoftLayer Its All Cloud: Blurring the Line Between Dedicated and Cloud Service Terremark Parting the Clouds - Evaluating Clouds and Cloud Providers for the Enterprise VMware An Evolutionary Path to Cloud Computing - VMwares Private, Public, and Hybrid Cloud Solutions Click For 2009 West Event Webcasts  Cloud Expo  Virtualization 2010 East PLATINUM PLUS SPONSORS: Abiquo Eliminate Vendor Lock-in with Next-Generation Virtualization Management Adaptivity Building the Cloud Blueprint for Enterprise IT GOLD SPONSORS: Cordys Continuous Business Transformation: The Cloud Value Chain Microsoft Microsofts Cloud Services Approach Navisite Defining Enterprise-Class Cloud Computing: Managed Cloud Services Surgient Deploy an Enterprise Private Cloud in Less Than 30 Days with Surgient Terremark Parting the Clouds - Evaluating Clouds and Cloud Providers for the Enterprise The Planet The Cloud’s Not the Revolution: Cloud Usage Is Unisys Storm Clouds - Disruptive Technologies Creating the New Normal Virtual Ark Third-Generation Outsourcing Is Here! Click For 2009 West Event Webcasts  Live Google News by SYS-CON! Top Three Links You Must Click On From the Wires Western Titanium Resolves Pending Charges By: PR Newswire Jan. 13, 2011 04:56 PM SAN DIEGO, Jan. 13, 2011 /PRNewswire/ -- Western Titanium, Inc. today announced that pending indictments against four current and former employees of the corporation, including CEO Daniel Schroeder, were dismissed mid-trial. These employees were charged with 19 felony counts, each related to allegations of the sale of nonconforming titanium. Western agreed to plead guilty to one count of the nineteen count indictment charging the company with selling material certified to AMS 4928Q, which had been superseded by AMS 4928R, and was cut from a cross section too large for the properties of the titanium to be uniform throughout and too large to provide the basis for informed scientific extrapolations as established by the data in the Metallic Materials Properties Development and Standardization handbook, formerly known as MIL Handbook 5. This mail fraud count related to a single shipment of titanium. All other charges against the company were dismissed. With respect to the charged count: 1) Westerns customer purchased the material from Westerns wholly owned subsidiary, Mach 2 Metals, and pre-approved cutting the titanium from a thicker forged block with a cross-section greater than 48 square inches, and 2) material integrity was not in question, as the titanium passed independent testing by a Pratt  Whitney LCS approved laboratory. After learning of the alleged nonconformance, Pratt  Whitneys internal investigation revealed there was no evidence of delivered material in PWs products which does not meet the metallurgical and mechanical properties of the AMS material specification. Western feels this settlement is in the best interest of the company and its customers, as it resolves all matters at issue in the investigation and avoids any further costs of litigation. Western looks forward to working with the Air Force to ensure that this type of compliance issue does not arise again, and to demonstrate its commitment to being a responsible subcontractor to the government. CONTACT: Nancy Luque, +1-202-841-3472, nluque@luquemarino.com SOURCE Western Titanium, Inc. Published Jan. 13, 2011 Copyright © 2011 SYS-CON Media, Inc. — All Rights Reserved. Syndicated stories and blog feeds, all rights reserved by the author. About PR Newswire Copyright © 2007 PR Newswire. All rights reserved. Republication or redistribution of PRNewswire content is expressly prohibited without the prior written consent of PRNewswire. PRNewswire shall not be liable for any errors or delays in the content, or for any actions taken in reliance thereon. Subscribe to the Worlds Most Powerful Newsletters Subscribe to Our Rss Feeds  Get Your SYS-CON News Live! Click to Add our RSS Feeds to the Service of Your Choice: View Additional SYS-CON Feeds Publish Your Article! Please send it to editorial(at)sys-con.com! Advertise on this site! Contact advertising(at)sys-con.com! 201 802-3021  SYS-CON Featured Whitepapers ADS BY GOOGLE  Breaking Java News ATW Gold Corp.: Name Change to Redhill Resources Corp. OnStar Looking for Application Developers of the Future C7 Technologies and Dalcon Communication Systems, Inc. Announce Partnership TeamStaff, Inc. Announces Delay of Year End Results Billionaire Alki David and Mike Mozart Release Second Incendiary CBS Video in Response to Leslie Moonves Comments American Capital Agency Corp. Announces Pricing of Public Offering of Common Stock The X-Change Corporation Completes the 2010 Audit and Files a 10k to Complete the Asset Purchase of 21-Century Silicon, Inc. LSSOs Legal Lean Sigma(TM) Process Improvement Certifications Help Legal Profession Increase Efficiency, Deliver Value and Boost Profits Seattle Lighting Receives First Batch of VU1 ESL Energy Efficient Light Bulbs INOVA Announces Sale to One of the Largest Operating Crews in Southern Iraq  ADVERTISE   |   MAGAZINE SUBSCRIPTIONS   |   FREE BREAKING-NEWSLETTERS!   |   SYS-CON.TV   |   BLOG-N-PLAY!   |   WEBCAST   |   EDUCATION   |   RESEARCH .NET Developers Journal - .NETDJ   |   ColdFusion Developers Journal - CFDJ   |   Eclipse Developers Journal - EDJ   |   Enterprise Open Source Magazine - EOS Open Web Developers Journal - OPENWEB   |   iPhone Developers Journal - iPHONE   |   Virtualization - Virtualization   |   Java Developers Journal - JDJ   |   Linux.SYS-CON.com PowerBuilder Developers Journal - PBDJ   |   SEO / SEM Journal - SJ   |   SOAWorld Magazine - SOAWM   |   IT Solutions Guide - ITSG   |   Symbian Developers Journal - SDJ WebLogic Developers Journal - WLDJ   |   WebSphere Journal - WJ   |   Wireless Business  Technology - WBT   |   XML-Journal - XMLJ   |   Internet Video - iTV Flex Developers Journal - Flex   |   AJAXWorld Magazine - AWM   |   Silverlight Developers Journal - SLDJ   |   PHP.SYS-CON.com   |   Web 2.0 Journal - WEB2 Apache   |   CMS   |   CRM   |   HP   |   Oracle Journal   |   Perl   |   Python   |   Red Hat   |   Ruby on Rails   |   SAP   |   SaaS SYS-CON MEDIA:   ABOUT US   |   CONTACT US   |   COMPANY NEWS   |   CAREERS   |   SITE MAP SYS-CON EVENTS:   |  AJAXWorld Conference  Expo  |  iPhone Developer Summit  |  Cloud Computing Conference  Expo  |  SOA World Conference  Expo  |  Virtualization Conference  Expo INTERNATIONAL SITES:   India  |  U.K.  |  Canada  |  Germany  |  France  |  Australia  |  Italy  |  Spain  |  Netherlands  |  Brazil  |  Belgium  Terms of Use  Our Privacy Statement     About Newsfeeds / Video Feeds Copyright ©1994-2008 SYS-CON Publications, Inc. All Rights Reserved. All marks are trademarks of SYS-CON Media. Reproduction in whole or in part in any form or medium without express written permission of SYS-CON Publications, Inc. is prohibited.    close this window</content></blog></root>