<root><blog><title>DC Designer Rochelle Behrens Lands on the Oprah Show : project beltway</title><content>DC Designer Rochelle Behrens Lands on the Oprah Show : project beltway home About DC Designer Rochelle Behrens Lands on the Oprah Show Thursday, January 13, 2011 Big ups to Rochelle Behrens, whose kinda-perfect no-gape shirts, aptly called The Shirt, are being featured rightthisminute (on the East Coast, at least) on the Oprah show. THE OPRAH SHOW YALL. I’ve been a fan of Rochelle and her designing skills since 2008, so I gladly volunteered to be a part of her current marketing campaign. Who among us HASN’T wondered why somebody out there can’t figure out how to make these dang shirts not gape? For that, we – and our lady lumps – thank you, Rochelle. Available online here. Comments Leave a Comment If you would like to make a comment, please fill out the form below. Name (required) Email (required) Website Comments Recently Written DC Designer Rochelle Behrens Lands on the Oprah Show Probably the first of many aspirational-spring-dressing posts Miami Take Two Welcome to Miami Jeggings for the rest of us Monthly Archives Select Month January 2011  (7) December 2010  (3) October 2010  (3) September 2010  (6) August 2010  (4) July 2010  (4) June 2010  (4) May 2010  (5) April 2010  (5) March 2010  (9) February 2010  (8) January 2010  (9) December 2009  (8) November 2009  (9) October 2009  (13) September 2009  (12) August 2009  (11) July 2009  (7) June 2009  (11) May 2009  (11) April 2009  (23) March 2009  (15) February 2009  (20) January 2009  (16) December 2008  (13) November 2008  (9) October 2008  (14) September 2008  (17) August 2008  (11) July 2008  (17) June 2008  (17) May 2008  (19) April 2008  (20) March 2008  (27) February 2008  (20) January 2008  (15) December 2007  (23) November 2007  (29) October 2007  (51) September 2007  (45) August 2007  (29) July 2007  (28) June 2007  (55) May 2007  (51) April 2007  (50) March 2007  (67) February 2007  (63) January 2007  (21) linkage PB Approved Route 7 Media Fashion  Style NYT’s On The Runway The Sartorialist Washington Post’s Off The Runway  Subscribe to our RSS Feed Find It backstage Log in Design site provided by route 7 media. original css coding by brian gardner.</content></blog></root>