Parkway Announces Leasing and Occupancy Update | SYS-CON MEDIA   Jump to a SYS-CON Magazine .NET Developers Journal apache.SYS-CON.com AjaxWorld Magazine - AWM Cloud Computing Journal cms.SYS-CON.com ColdFusion Developers Journal crm.SYS-CON.com Eclipse Developers Journal Enterprise Open Source Magazine Flex Developers Journal - Flex HP.SYS-CON.com Internet Video - iTV iPhone Developers Journal - iPHONE IT Solutions Guide Java Developers Journal Linux.SYS-CON.com Open Web Developers Journal oracle.SYS-CON.com perl.SYS-CON.com PHP.SYS-CON.com PowerBuilder Developers Journal python.SYS-CON.com redhat.SYS-CON.com ruby.SYS-CON.com SEO/SEM (Search) Journal Silverlight Developers Journal saas.SYS-CON.com SAP.SYS-CON.com SOAWorld Magazine - SWM Symbian Developers Journal Virtualization.SYS-CON.com Web 2.0 Journal WebLogic Journal WebSphere Journal Wireless Business  Technology XML Journal The i-Technology Media! Register | Log in       .NET  ·  AJAX  ·  CLOUD  ·  ECLIPSE  ·  FLEX  ·  OPEN WEB  ·  iPHONE  ·  JAVA  ·  LINUX  ·  OPEN SOURCE  ·  ORACLE  ·  PBDJ  ·  SEARCH  ·  SILVERLIGHT  ·  SOA  ·  VIRTUALIZATION  ·  WEB 2.0  ·  WIRELESS  ·  XML Comments Web 2.0 Is Dead. Long Live Web 2.0! By Fuat Kircaali rabcraig wrote: I regret what i said, i dont think that Craigslist has to improve, theyre really simplistic and you can search classifieds like you would do in a newspaper. Dec. 29, 2010 06:59 PM EST read more  respond » Cloud Expo on Google News  Did you read todays front page stories  breaking news?  Cloud Expo  Virtualization 2010 West DIAMOND SPONSOR: Oracle Roadmap to Enterprise Cloud Computing PLATINUM PLUS SPONSORS: Abiquo Next Generation Cloud Management - Introducing the Virtual Enterprise Adaptivity The Enterprise Cloud Lifecycle Microsoft The Move is On: Cloud Strategies for Businesses PLATINUM SPONSORS: Red Hat Unlocking the Value of the Cloud Today SAP The Journey to On Demand - Lessons Learned from Small, High-Growth Customers Unisys What if You Could Transform IT Your Way, Using Cloud 2.0? GOLD SPONSORS: CA Technologies. Changing the Game: How to Get a Cloud Service Up and Running in Less Than 30 Days Cisco Cisco Cloud Strategy, Within and Across Data Centers Compuware Borderless Applications: The Future of Performance in the Cloud Cordys The Business Value of the Cloud Intel Next Cloud on the Horizon: Exascale to Microservers Navisite Cloud Computing – Extending Your IT Infrastructure Quest Software The Private Cloud in Practice: Case Studies  Proven Strategies Rackspace Hosting OpenStack for the Enterprise SoftLayer Its All Cloud: Blurring the Line Between Dedicated and Cloud Service Terremark Parting the Clouds - Evaluating Clouds and Cloud Providers for the Enterprise VMware An Evolutionary Path to Cloud Computing - VMwares Private, Public, and Hybrid Cloud Solutions Click For 2009 West Event Webcasts  Cloud Expo  Virtualization 2010 East PLATINUM PLUS SPONSORS: Abiquo Eliminate Vendor Lock-in with Next-Generation Virtualization Management Adaptivity Building the Cloud Blueprint for Enterprise IT GOLD SPONSORS: Cordys Continuous Business Transformation: The Cloud Value Chain Microsoft Microsofts Cloud Services Approach Navisite Defining Enterprise-Class Cloud Computing: Managed Cloud Services Surgient Deploy an Enterprise Private Cloud in Less Than 30 Days with Surgient Terremark Parting the Clouds - Evaluating Clouds and Cloud Providers for the Enterprise The Planet The Cloud’s Not the Revolution: Cloud Usage Is Unisys Storm Clouds - Disruptive Technologies Creating the New Normal Virtual Ark Third-Generation Outsourcing Is Here! Click For 2009 West Event Webcasts  Live Google News by SYS-CON! Top Three Links You Must Click On From the Wires Parkway Announces Leasing and Occupancy Update By: PR Newswire Jan. 13, 2011 05:21 PM JACKSON, Miss., Jan. 13, 2011 /PRNewswire/ -- Parkway Properties, Inc. (NYSE: PKY) announced today that it signed a total of 178,000 square feet of new leases, 594,000 square feet of renewal leases, and 46,000 square feet of expansion leases during the fourth quarter of 2010. Key metrics associated with this activity will be disclosed in the Companys fourth quarter 2010 earnings press release and supplemental package. Additionally, Parkway currently anticipates customers occupying approximately 431,000 square feet to either vacate or contract upon lease expiration during the first quarter of 2011. This represents 3.3% of the total portfolio and 71.0% of total first quarter lease expirations. The Companys portfolio is currently 85.6% occupied. After accounting for recent leasing activity, and offset by known move-outs, Parkways portfolio is anticipated to be 83.4% leased as shown in the attached exhibit. This leased percentage does not include pending leasing activity for leases not yet signed, and Parkway anticipates 2011 leasing volume to be in line with historical levels. William R. Flatt, Chief Operating Officer at Parkway, stated, We expect our occupancy to decline during the first quarter of 2011 due to a larger than normal amount of known move-outs and contractions, the majority of which have either been previously disclosed or will not have a negative impact on cash income in 2011. We continue to see encouraging levels of new and expansion leasing activity and anticipate our occupancy to begin to recover after the first quarter. Major leases greater than 20,000 square feet signed during the fourth quarter of 2010 include: Blue Cross Blue Shield of Georgia, Inc. (BCBS of GA) signed a 126 month renewal for 199,000 square feet which commenced January 1, 2011, at One Capital City Plaza in Atlanta, Georgia. This renewal included a contraction of 53,000 square feet effective upon commencement. The new rental rate per square foot increases in 2011 such that total cash income does not decline in 2011, despite the contraction. However, the effective rental rate per square foot over the entire term of the renewal is in-line with the prior in-place rate. Motorola, Inc. signed a four year renewal for 53,000 square feet commencing April 1, 2011, at 233 North Michigan in Chicago, Illinois. This renewal includes a contraction of 15,000 square feet effective upon commencement. A major national health insurance carrier signed a five year new lease for 46,000 square feet commencing May 1, 2011, at Peachtree Dunwoody Pavilion in Atlanta, Georgia. This new customer will occupy a portion of the space to be vacated by Autotrader.com during the first quarter. National Council of State Boards of Nurses signed a 111 month renewal for 29,000 square feet and expanded by 6,000 square feet commencing May 1, 2012, at 111 East Wacker in Chicago, Illinois. Intercall, Inc. signed a 94 month renewal for 28,000 square feet commencing May 1, 2011, at US Cellular Plaza in Chicago, Illinois. Brenntag Latin America, Inc. signed a 134 month renewal for 25,000 square feet commencing February 1, 2011, at 5300 Memorial Building in Houston, Texas. Dart Container Sales Company signed a seven year renewal for 20,000 square feet and expanded by 4,000 square feet commencing February 1, 2011, at Hillsboro Center V in Fort Lauderdale, Florida. Mid-Atlantic Convenience Stores signed a 69 month new lease for 23,000 square feet which commenced December 27, 2010, at Boulders Center in Richmond, Virginia. Full Sail, Inc. signed a 64 month new lease for 22,000 square feet commencing January 16, 2011, at Gateway Center in Orlando, Florida. Major known move-outs greater than 20,000 square feet during the first quarter of 2011 include: AutoTrader.com will vacate 193,000 square feet on February 28, 2011, at Peachtree Dunwoody Pavilion in Atlanta, Georgia. United States Attorneys Office is expected to vacate 31,000 square feet on February 28, 2011, at One Jackson Place in Jackson, Mississippi. US Bankruptcy Court is expected to vacate 29,000 square feet on March 31, 2011, at Parking at Jackson Place in Jackson, Mississippi. Supportive Oncology Services, Inc will vacate 25,000 square feet on January 14, 2011, at Forum II  III in Memphis, Tennessee. AAM, LLC will contract by 23,000 square feet on January 31, 2011, at Squaw Peak Corporate Center I in Phoenix, Arizona. Digital Risk, LLC will vacate 20,000 square feet on January 31, 2011, at Gateway Center in Orlando, Florida. About Parkway Properties Parkway Properties, Inc., a member of the SP Small Cap 600 Index, is a self-administered real estate investment trust specializing in the operation, leasing, acquisition, and ownership of office properties. The Company is geographically focused on the Southeastern and Southwestern United States and Chicago. Parkway owns or has an interest in 64 office properties located in 11 states with an aggregate of approximately 13.2 million square feet of leasable space as of January 13, 2011. Included in the portfolio are 20 properties totaling 3.7 million square feet that are owned jointly with other investors, representing 28.0% of the portfolio. Fee-based real estate services are offered through the Companys wholly-owned subsidiary, Parkway Realty Services, which also manages and/or leases approximately 1.8 million square feet for third-party owners at January 13, 2011. Parkway Properties, Inc.s press releases and additional information about the Company are available on the Companys website at http://www.pky.com. Forward Looking Statement Certain statements in this release that are not in the present or past tense or discuss the Companys expectations (including the use of the words anticipate, believe, forecast, intends or project) are forward-looking statements within the meaning of the federal securities laws and as such are based upon the Companys current belief as to the outcome and timing of future events. There can be no assurance that future developments affecting the Company will be those anticipated by the Company. These forward-looking statements involve risks and uncertainties (some of which are beyond the control of the Company) and are subject to change based upon various factors, including but not limited to the following risks and uncertainties: changes in the real estate industry and in performance of the financial markets; the demand for and market acceptance of the Companys properties for rental purposes; the amount and growth of the Companys expenses; tenant financial difficulties and general economic conditions, including interest rates, as well as economic conditions in those areas where the Company owns properties; risks associated with joint venture partners; the risks associated with the ownership and development of real property; the failure to acquire or sell properties as and when anticipated; the outcome of claims and litigation involving or affecting the Company; and other risks and uncertainties detailed from time to time in the Companys SEC filings. Should one or more of these risks or uncertainties occur, or should underlying assumptions prove incorrect, the Companys results could differ materially from those expressed in the forward-looking statements. The Company does not undertake to update forward-looking statements.     

                                           Parkway Properties, Inc.
                                                Leasing Status
                                                   1/7/2011

                                               Wholly     Consolidated   Unconsolidated
                                                Owned          JVs             JVs          Total
                                                -----          ---             ---          -----

                       Occupancy Percentage
                                   01/01/11        86.8%          82.2%            82.3%       85.6%
                      ---------------------        ----           ----             ----        ----

                    Total Square Footage      9,506,668      3,285,215          403,753  13,195,636
                    Vacancy (A)               1,251,446        584,180           71,433   1,907,059


                                        Signed Leases Not Yet Commenced
                                        -------------------------------
                                                                                                     Commencement
                                                                                                     ------------
          City              Building                             Square Feet                      Quarter  Year
          ----              --------                             -----------                      -------  ----
                     Peachtree Dunwoody
    Atlanta, GA      Pavilion                    46,232                                      46,232        2   2011
    Charlotte, NC   Carmel Crossing-Davie                        4,830                        4,830        1   2011
    Charlotte, NC   Carmel Crossing-Davie                        1,809                        1,809        1   2011
    Chicago, IL     233 North Michigan Ave        2,739                                       2,739        1   2011
    Chicago, IL     US Cellular Plaza                            5,172                        5,172        2   2011
    Chicago, IL     US Cellular Plaza                            8,082                        8,082        2   2011
    Columbia, SC    Tower at 1301 Gervais         4,090                                       4,090        1   2011
    Ft. Lauderdale,
     FL             Hillsboro Center V            3,571                                       3,571        1   2011
    Houston, TX     1401 Enclave                                12,183                       12,183        1   2011
    Houston, TX     5300 Memorial Building          503                                         503        1   2011
    Houston, TX     5300 Memorial Building        2,836                                       2,836        2   2011
    Houston, TX     Comerica Bank Building        2,997                                       2,997        1   2011
    Houston, TX     Comerica Bank Building        1,047                                       1,047        1   2011
    Houston, TX     Town and Country                686                                         686        1   2011
                     Parking at Jackson
    Jackson, MS      Place                          879                                         879        1   2011
    Jackson, MS     111 Capitol Building            755                                         755        2   2012
    Memphis, TN     Forum II  III                1,476                                       1,476        1   2011
    Memphis, TN     Forum II  III                4,173                                       4,173        1   2011
    Orlando, FL     Gateway Center                              21,834                       21,834        1   2011
    Orlando, FL     Gateway Center                              17,309                       17,309        1   2011
                     Desert Ridge Corp
    Phoenix, AZ      Center I                                    3,706                        3,706        1   2011
                     Squaw Peak Corp Center
    Phoenix, AZ      I                            3,406                                       3,406        2   2011

                     Sum of signed leases
                     (B)                         75,390         74,925                -     150,315
                                                 ------         ------              ---     -------



                                           Leases Expected to Vacate
                                           -------------------------
                                                                                                      Expiration
                                                                                                      ----------
          City              Building                             Square Feet                      Quarter  Year
          ----              --------                             -----------                      -------  ----
    Atlanta, GA     Peachtree Ridge                              4,342                        4,342        1   2011
                     Peachtree Dunwoody
    Atlanta, GA      Pavilion                   193,043                                     193,043        1   2011
                     Peachtree Dunwoody
    Atlanta, GA      Pavilion                     4,974                                       4,974        1   2011
                     Peachtree Dunwoody
    Atlanta, GA      Pavilion                     9,963                                       9,963        1   2011
    Chicago, IL     233 North Michigan           14,577                                      14,577        1   2011
    Hampton Roads,
     VA             Greenbrier Tower II           1,772                                       1,772        1   2011
    Houston, TX     5300 Memorial                 1,958                                       1,958        1   2011
    Houston, TX     Woodbranch                      987                                         987        1   2011
    Houston, TX     Woodbranch                    3,860                                       3,860        1   2011
    Houston, TX     Sugar Grove                   1,783                                       1,783        1   2011
    Jackson, MS     111 Capitol Building          3,660                                       3,660        1   2011
    Jackson, MS     City Centre                   4,978                                       4,978        1   2011
    Jackson, MS     City Centre                  16,873                                      16,873        1   2011
    Jackson, MS     One Jackson Place            30,909                                      30,909        1   2011
                     Parking at Jackson
    Jackson, MS      Place                       29,061                                      29,061        1   2011
    Memphis, TN     Forum I                       2,739                                       2,739        1   2011
    Memphis, TN     Forum II  III               24,658                                      24,658        1   2011
    Memphis, TN     Morgan Keegan Tower           1,780                                       1,780        1   2011
    Orlando, FL     Gateway Center                              20,334                       20,334        1   2011
    Orlando, FL     Maitland 200                                                  1,630       1,630        1   2011
                     Desert Ridge Corporate
    Phoenix, AZ      Center I                                    1,420                        1,420        1   2011
    Phoenix, AZ     Mesa Corporate Center        11,264                                      11,264        1   2011
                     Squaw Peak Corporate
    Phoenix, AZ      Center I                    22,543                                      22,543        1   2011
                     Squaw Peak Corporate
    Phoenix, AZ      Center II                   13,399                                      13,399        1   2011
    Richmond, VA    Moorefield I                  6,712                                       6,712        1   2011
    Richmond, VA    Moorefield I                    741                                         741        1   2011
    Richmond, VA    Winchester Building             883                                         883        1   2011

                     Sum of vacating leases
                     (C)                        403,117         26,096            1,630     430,843
                                                -------         ------            -----     -------

                     Adjusted Vacancy (A -B
                      + C)                    1,579,173        535,351           73,063   2,187,587
                                              =========        =======           ======   =========
                     Total Square Footage     9,506,668      3,285,215          403,753  13,195,636

                     Leased Percentage             83.4%          83.7%            81.9%       83.4%
                     -----------------             ----           ----             ----        ----

    
 

    CONTACT:          RICHARD G. HICKSON IV
                      CHIEF FINANCIAL OFFICER
                      WILLIAM R. FLATT
                      CHIEF OPERATING OFFICER
                      (601) 948-4091

 SOURCE Parkway Properties, Inc. Published Jan. 13, 2011 Copyright © 2011 SYS-CON Media, Inc. — All Rights Reserved. Syndicated stories and blog feeds, all rights reserved by the author. About PR Newswire Copyright © 2007 PR Newswire. All rights reserved. Republication or redistribution of PRNewswire content is expressly prohibited without the prior written consent of PRNewswire. PRNewswire shall not be liable for any errors or delays in the content, or for any actions taken in reliance thereon. Subscribe to the Worlds Most Powerful Newsletters Subscribe to Our Rss Feeds  Get Your SYS-CON News Live! Click to Add our RSS Feeds to the Service of Your Choice: View Additional SYS-CON Feeds Publish Your Article! Please send it to editorial(at)sys-con.com! Advertise on this site! Contact advertising(at)sys-con.com! 201 802-3021  SYS-CON Featured Whitepapers ADS BY GOOGLE  Breaking Java News ATW Gold Corp.: Name Change to Redhill Resources Corp. OnStar Looking for Application Developers of the Future C7 Technologies and Dalcon Communication Systems, Inc. Announce Partnership TeamStaff, Inc. Announces Delay of Year End Results Billionaire Alki David and Mike Mozart Release Second Incendiary CBS Video in Response to Leslie Moonves Comments American Capital Agency Corp. Announces Pricing of Public Offering of Common Stock The X-Change Corporation Completes the 2010 Audit and Files a 10k to Complete the Asset Purchase of 21-Century Silicon, Inc. LSSOs Legal Lean Sigma(TM) Process Improvement Certifications Help Legal Profession Increase Efficiency, Deliver Value and Boost Profits Seattle Lighting Receives First Batch of VU1 ESL Energy Efficient Light Bulbs INOVA Announces Sale to One of the Largest Operating Crews in Southern Iraq  ADVERTISE   |   MAGAZINE SUBSCRIPTIONS   |   FREE BREAKING-NEWSLETTERS!   |   SYS-CON.TV   |   BLOG-N-PLAY!   |   WEBCAST   |   EDUCATION   |   RESEARCH .NET Developers Journal - .NETDJ   |   ColdFusion Developers Journal - CFDJ   |   Eclipse Developers Journal - EDJ   |   Enterprise Open Source Magazine - EOS Open Web Developers Journal - OPENWEB   |   iPhone Developers Journal - iPHONE   |   Virtualization - Virtualization   |   Java Developers Journal - JDJ   |   Linux.SYS-CON.com PowerBuilder Developers Journal - PBDJ   |   SEO / SEM Journal - SJ   |   SOAWorld Magazine - SOAWM   |   IT Solutions Guide - ITSG   |   Symbian Developers Journal - SDJ WebLogic Developers Journal - WLDJ   |   WebSphere Journal - WJ   |   Wireless Business  Technology - WBT   |   XML-Journal - XMLJ   |   Internet Video - iTV Flex Developers Journal - Flex   |   AJAXWorld Magazine - AWM   |   Silverlight Developers Journal - SLDJ   |   PHP.SYS-CON.com   |   Web 2.0 Journal - WEB2 Apache   |   CMS   |   CRM   |   HP   |   Oracle Journal   |   Perl   |   Python   |   Red Hat   |   Ruby on Rails   |   SAP   |   SaaS SYS-CON MEDIA:   ABOUT US   |   CONTACT US   |   COMPANY NEWS   |   CAREERS   |   SITE MAP SYS-CON EVENTS:   |  AJAXWorld Conference  Expo  |  iPhone Developer Summit  |  Cloud Computing Conference  Expo  |  SOA World Conference  Expo  |  Virtualization Conference  Expo INTERNATIONAL SITES:   India  |  U.K.  |  Canada  |  Germany  |  France  |  Australia  |  Italy  |  Spain  |  Netherlands  |  Brazil  |  Belgium  Terms of Use  Our Privacy Statement     About Newsfeeds / Video Feeds Copyright ©1994-2008 SYS-CON Publications, Inc. All Rights Reserved. All marks are trademarks of SYS-CON Media. Reproduction in whole or in part in any form or medium without express written permission of SYS-CON Publications, Inc. is prohibited.    close this window