INOVA Announces Sale to One of the Largest Operating Crews in Southern Iraq | SYS-CON MEDIA   Jump to a SYS-CON Magazine .NET Developers Journal apache.SYS-CON.com AjaxWorld Magazine - AWM Cloud Computing Journal cms.SYS-CON.com ColdFusion Developers Journal crm.SYS-CON.com Eclipse Developers Journal Enterprise Open Source Magazine Flex Developers Journal - Flex HP.SYS-CON.com Internet Video - iTV iPhone Developers Journal - iPHONE IT Solutions Guide Java Developers Journal Linux.SYS-CON.com Open Web Developers Journal oracle.SYS-CON.com perl.SYS-CON.com PHP.SYS-CON.com PowerBuilder Developers Journal python.SYS-CON.com redhat.SYS-CON.com ruby.SYS-CON.com SEO/SEM (Search) Journal Silverlight Developers Journal saas.SYS-CON.com SAP.SYS-CON.com SOAWorld Magazine - SWM Symbian Developers Journal Virtualization.SYS-CON.com Web 2.0 Journal WebLogic Journal WebSphere Journal Wireless Business  Technology XML Journal The i-Technology Media! Register | Log in       .NET  ·  AJAX  ·  CLOUD  ·  ECLIPSE  ·  FLEX  ·  OPEN WEB  ·  iPHONE  ·  JAVA  ·  LINUX  ·  OPEN SOURCE  ·  ORACLE  ·  PBDJ  ·  SEARCH  ·  SILVERLIGHT  ·  SOA  ·  VIRTUALIZATION  ·  WEB 2.0  ·  WIRELESS  ·  XML Comments Web 2.0 Is Dead. Long Live Web 2.0! By Fuat Kircaali rabcraig wrote: I regret what i said, i dont think that Craigslist has to improve, theyre really simplistic and you can search classifieds like you would do in a newspaper. Dec. 29, 2010 06:59 PM EST read more  respond » Cloud Expo on Google News  Did you read todays front page stories  breaking news?  Cloud Expo  Virtualization 2010 West DIAMOND SPONSOR: Oracle Roadmap to Enterprise Cloud Computing PLATINUM PLUS SPONSORS: Abiquo Next Generation Cloud Management - Introducing the Virtual Enterprise Adaptivity The Enterprise Cloud Lifecycle Microsoft The Move is On: Cloud Strategies for Businesses PLATINUM SPONSORS: Red Hat Unlocking the Value of the Cloud Today SAP The Journey to On Demand - Lessons Learned from Small, High-Growth Customers Unisys What if You Could Transform IT Your Way, Using Cloud 2.0? GOLD SPONSORS: CA Technologies. Changing the Game: How to Get a Cloud Service Up and Running in Less Than 30 Days Cisco Cisco Cloud Strategy, Within and Across Data Centers Compuware Borderless Applications: The Future of Performance in the Cloud Cordys The Business Value of the Cloud Intel Next Cloud on the Horizon: Exascale to Microservers Navisite Cloud Computing – Extending Your IT Infrastructure Quest Software The Private Cloud in Practice: Case Studies  Proven Strategies Rackspace Hosting OpenStack for the Enterprise SoftLayer Its All Cloud: Blurring the Line Between Dedicated and Cloud Service Terremark Parting the Clouds - Evaluating Clouds and Cloud Providers for the Enterprise VMware An Evolutionary Path to Cloud Computing - VMwares Private, Public, and Hybrid Cloud Solutions Click For 2009 West Event Webcasts  Cloud Expo  Virtualization 2010 East PLATINUM PLUS SPONSORS: Abiquo Eliminate Vendor Lock-in with Next-Generation Virtualization Management Adaptivity Building the Cloud Blueprint for Enterprise IT GOLD SPONSORS: Cordys Continuous Business Transformation: The Cloud Value Chain Microsoft Microsofts Cloud Services Approach Navisite Defining Enterprise-Class Cloud Computing: Managed Cloud Services Surgient Deploy an Enterprise Private Cloud in Less Than 30 Days with Surgient Terremark Parting the Clouds - Evaluating Clouds and Cloud Providers for the Enterprise The Planet The Cloud’s Not the Revolution: Cloud Usage Is Unisys Storm Clouds - Disruptive Technologies Creating the New Normal Virtual Ark Third-Generation Outsourcing Is Here! Click For 2009 West Event Webcasts  Live Google News by SYS-CON! Top Three Links You Must Click On From the Wires INOVA Announces Sale to One of the Largest Operating Crews in Southern Iraq By: PR Newswire Jan. 13, 2011 05:42 PM HOUSTON, Jan. 13, 2011 /PRNewswire/ -- INOVA Geophysical Equipment Limited today announced a 2010 fourth quarter sale of 13,000 channels of ARIES II, INOVAs cable based land recording system, to Dubai based Terraseis. The deal also includes the sale of 39,000 SM-24XL geophone strings from the Sensor subsidiary of ION Geophysical, for which INOVA is a channel partner. The system will be used by one of the largest operating crews in Southern Iraq. Deployment of the equipment commenced in Q4 of 2010 and the system is expected to be fully deployed in Q1 of 2011. Kevin Plintz, founder and chairman of the board for Terraseis commented, Most of our projects are typically undertaken in challenging geophysical environments. In these circumstances, its critical that we ensure our crews are equipped to operate efficiently and we count on reliable equipment. We need to ensure that our suppliers are available with support from the moment our crews hit the ground, helping us deliver the ultimate success of a project. Weve used ARIES II for other projects and feel confident in the performance that it delivers. We also are encouraged by the level of support and trusted service that INOVA provides with their equipment. Steve Bate, President and Chief Executive Officer of INOVA, added, This transaction continues to solidify our partnership with one of the largest global seismic service providers. The quality and reliability of our equipment helps our customers meet the demanding conditions of seismic acquisition today, and Terraseis believes in providing its customers with the best service and equipment available in the market. As we expand our footprint in these regions, we are committed to providing excellent products and services in our relationship with Terraseis, and this recent sale is just one more example. Richard Forrest-Hill, Vice President of IONs Holland-based Sensor B.V. subsidiary, added, We are proud to partner with Terraseis on such a significant project and also to have participated in this transaction with our colleagues at INOVA. Our goal is to bring added value to our customers operations by supplying them best in class equipment and support. Our SM-24XL geophone has been designed and manufactured to deliver high quality data capture in any operating climate or environment and is indicative of our commitment to customer satisfaction. We look forward to many more such collaborations enabling us to deliver high quality products and services to our customers. INOVAs ARIES II land acquisition system is designed to maximize return on investment by reducing equipment related downtime and minimizing the impact of harsh environmental and operational conditions. It supports high channel count, advanced vibroseis acquisition for all 2D, 3D, or time-lapse 4D seismic programs. Learn more about ARIES II and INOVAs other land recording systems at www.inovageo.com About INOVA Geophysical Equipment Limited INOVA Geophysical Equipment Limited is a leading provider of land geophysical technology, including source and source control systems, cabled and cableless land acquisition systems, and advanced seismic sensing devices. Managed as an independent company, INOVA is a joint venture owned 51% by BGP (a wholly owned subsidiary of China National Petroleum Corporation) and 49% by ION Geophysical Corporation (NYSE: IO). Additional information about INOVA is available at www.inovageo.com. About Terraseis Terraseis is one of the fastest growing providers of geophysical data acquisition services to international exploration and production companies in the Middle East, Asia and Africa with most recent focus in Kurdish Region of Iraq and West Africa. Terraseis is a widely recognized leader in acquiring seismic data in particularly challenging geographic, economic and political environments and in working with clients requiring complex and demanding services agreements. Additional information about Terraseis is available at www.terraseis.com 

    CONTACTS
    INOVA
    Mr. Fernando Hernandez
    Director of Marketing
    Phone: +1.281.879.3559

 SOURCE INOVA Geophysical Equipment Limited Published Jan. 13, 2011 Copyright © 2011 SYS-CON Media, Inc. — All Rights Reserved. Syndicated stories and blog feeds, all rights reserved by the author. About PR Newswire Copyright © 2007 PR Newswire. All rights reserved. Republication or redistribution of PRNewswire content is expressly prohibited without the prior written consent of PRNewswire. PRNewswire shall not be liable for any errors or delays in the content, or for any actions taken in reliance thereon. Subscribe to the Worlds Most Powerful Newsletters Subscribe to Our Rss Feeds  Get Your SYS-CON News Live! Click to Add our RSS Feeds to the Service of Your Choice: View Additional SYS-CON Feeds Publish Your Article! Please send it to editorial(at)sys-con.com! Advertise on this site! Contact advertising(at)sys-con.com! 201 802-3021  SYS-CON Featured Whitepapers ADS BY GOOGLE  Breaking Java News ATW Gold Corp.: Name Change to Redhill Resources Corp. OnStar Looking for Application Developers of the Future C7 Technologies and Dalcon Communication Systems, Inc. Announce Partnership TeamStaff, Inc. Announces Delay of Year End Results Billionaire Alki David and Mike Mozart Release Second Incendiary CBS Video in Response to Leslie Moonves Comments American Capital Agency Corp. Announces Pricing of Public Offering of Common Stock The X-Change Corporation Completes the 2010 Audit and Files a 10k to Complete the Asset Purchase of 21-Century Silicon, Inc. LSSOs Legal Lean Sigma(TM) Process Improvement Certifications Help Legal Profession Increase Efficiency, Deliver Value and Boost Profits Seattle Lighting Receives First Batch of VU1 ESL Energy Efficient Light Bulbs INOVA Announces Sale to One of the Largest Operating Crews in Southern Iraq  ADVERTISE   |   MAGAZINE SUBSCRIPTIONS   |   FREE BREAKING-NEWSLETTERS!   |   SYS-CON.TV   |   BLOG-N-PLAY!   |   WEBCAST   |   EDUCATION   |   RESEARCH .NET Developers Journal - .NETDJ   |   ColdFusion Developers Journal - CFDJ   |   Eclipse Developers Journal - EDJ   |   Enterprise Open Source Magazine - EOS Open Web Developers Journal - OPENWEB   |   iPhone Developers Journal - iPHONE   |   Virtualization - Virtualization   |   Java Developers Journal - JDJ   |   Linux.SYS-CON.com PowerBuilder Developers Journal - PBDJ   |   SEO / SEM Journal - SJ   |   SOAWorld Magazine - SOAWM   |   IT Solutions Guide - ITSG   |   Symbian Developers Journal - SDJ WebLogic Developers Journal - WLDJ   |   WebSphere Journal - WJ   |   Wireless Business  Technology - WBT   |   XML-Journal - XMLJ   |   Internet Video - iTV Flex Developers Journal - Flex   |   AJAXWorld Magazine - AWM   |   Silverlight Developers Journal - SLDJ   |   PHP.SYS-CON.com   |   Web 2.0 Journal - WEB2 Apache   |   CMS   |   CRM   |   HP   |   Oracle Journal   |   Perl   |   Python   |   Red Hat   |   Ruby on Rails   |   SAP   |   SaaS SYS-CON MEDIA:   ABOUT US   |   CONTACT US   |   COMPANY NEWS   |   CAREERS   |   SITE MAP SYS-CON EVENTS:   |  AJAXWorld Conference  Expo  |  iPhone Developer Summit  |  Cloud Computing Conference  Expo  |  SOA World Conference  Expo  |  Virtualization Conference  Expo INTERNATIONAL SITES:   India  |  U.K.  |  Canada  |  Germany  |  France  |  Australia  |  Italy  |  Spain  |  Netherlands  |  Brazil  |  Belgium  Terms of Use  Our Privacy Statement     About Newsfeeds / Video Feeds Copyright ©1994-2008 SYS-CON Publications, Inc. All Rights Reserved. All marks are trademarks of SYS-CON Media. Reproduction in whole or in part in any form or medium without express written permission of SYS-CON Publications, Inc. is prohibited.    close this window