Merger Creates One Global Management Consulting Firm Committed to Measurable Results: Kurt Salmon | SYS-CON MEDIA   Jump to a SYS-CON Magazine .NET Developers Journal apache.SYS-CON.com AjaxWorld Magazine - AWM Cloud Computing Journal cms.SYS-CON.com ColdFusion Developers Journal crm.SYS-CON.com Eclipse Developers Journal Enterprise Open Source Magazine Flex Developers Journal - Flex HP.SYS-CON.com Internet Video - iTV iPhone Developers Journal - iPHONE IT Solutions Guide Java Developers Journal Linux.SYS-CON.com Open Web Developers Journal oracle.SYS-CON.com perl.SYS-CON.com PHP.SYS-CON.com PowerBuilder Developers Journal python.SYS-CON.com redhat.SYS-CON.com ruby.SYS-CON.com SEO/SEM (Search) Journal Silverlight Developers Journal saas.SYS-CON.com SAP.SYS-CON.com SOAWorld Magazine - SWM Symbian Developers Journal Virtualization.SYS-CON.com Web 2.0 Journal WebLogic Journal WebSphere Journal Wireless Business  Technology XML Journal The i-Technology Media! Register | Log in       .NET  ·  AJAX  ·  CLOUD  ·  ECLIPSE  ·  FLEX  ·  OPEN WEB  ·  iPHONE  ·  JAVA  ·  LINUX  ·  OPEN SOURCE  ·  ORACLE  ·  PBDJ  ·  SEARCH  ·  SILVERLIGHT  ·  SOA  ·  VIRTUALIZATION  ·  WEB 2.0  ·  WIRELESS  ·  XML Comments Web 2.0 Is Dead. Long Live Web 2.0! By Fuat Kircaali rabcraig wrote: I regret what i said, i dont think that Craigslist has to improve, theyre really simplistic and you can search classifieds like you would do in a newspaper. Dec. 29, 2010 06:59 PM EST read more  respond » Cloud Expo on Google News  Did you read todays front page stories  breaking news?  Cloud Expo  Virtualization 2010 West DIAMOND SPONSOR: Oracle Roadmap to Enterprise Cloud Computing PLATINUM PLUS SPONSORS: Abiquo Next Generation Cloud Management - Introducing the Virtual Enterprise Adaptivity The Enterprise Cloud Lifecycle Microsoft The Move is On: Cloud Strategies for Businesses PLATINUM SPONSORS: Red Hat Unlocking the Value of the Cloud Today SAP The Journey to On Demand - Lessons Learned from Small, High-Growth Customers Unisys What if You Could Transform IT Your Way, Using Cloud 2.0? GOLD SPONSORS: CA Technologies. Changing the Game: How to Get a Cloud Service Up and Running in Less Than 30 Days Cisco Cisco Cloud Strategy, Within and Across Data Centers Compuware Borderless Applications: The Future of Performance in the Cloud Cordys The Business Value of the Cloud Intel Next Cloud on the Horizon: Exascale to Microservers Navisite Cloud Computing – Extending Your IT Infrastructure Quest Software The Private Cloud in Practice: Case Studies  Proven Strategies Rackspace Hosting OpenStack for the Enterprise SoftLayer Its All Cloud: Blurring the Line Between Dedicated and Cloud Service Terremark Parting the Clouds - Evaluating Clouds and Cloud Providers for the Enterprise VMware An Evolutionary Path to Cloud Computing - VMwares Private, Public, and Hybrid Cloud Solutions Click For 2009 West Event Webcasts  Cloud Expo  Virtualization 2010 East PLATINUM PLUS SPONSORS: Abiquo Eliminate Vendor Lock-in with Next-Generation Virtualization Management Adaptivity Building the Cloud Blueprint for Enterprise IT GOLD SPONSORS: Cordys Continuous Business Transformation: The Cloud Value Chain Microsoft Microsofts Cloud Services Approach Navisite Defining Enterprise-Class Cloud Computing: Managed Cloud Services Surgient Deploy an Enterprise Private Cloud in Less Than 30 Days with Surgient Terremark Parting the Clouds - Evaluating Clouds and Cloud Providers for the Enterprise The Planet The Cloud’s Not the Revolution: Cloud Usage Is Unisys Storm Clouds - Disruptive Technologies Creating the New Normal Virtual Ark Third-Generation Outsourcing Is Here! Click For 2009 West Event Webcasts  Live Google News by SYS-CON! Top Three Links You Must Click On From the Wires Merger Creates One Global Management Consulting Firm Committed to Measurable Results: Kurt Salmon By: Business Wire Jan. 13, 2011 05:30 PM Kurt Salmon has solidified its position as a leading global management and strategy consultancy through the recently completed merger of Ineum Consulting and Kurt Salmon Associates. Kurt Salmon has over 1,600 consultants with offices throughout the world. In May 2010, both companies decided to merge and, since then, have collaborated on numerous client projects and achieved significant synergies through the combination. As the trusted advisor to industry leaders around the world, Kurt Salmon delivers measureable results through unparalleled specialization and executional excellence. By joining workforces, corporate heritages, and capabilities, the new Kurt Salmon firm is a unique global player with a proven track record in business strategy development, process enhancement, business transformation, and information systems. Kurt Salmon is an independent, agnostic consultancy of experienced advisors who are recognized as experts in their fields. This expertise, combined with deep highly specialized knowledge of its clients’ businesses, particularly within the Retail/Consumer and Financial Services sectors, are what enables Kurt Salmon to deliver unsurpassed client results. “The creation of Kurt Salmon is the achievement of an ambitious project guided by the search for excellence in our consulting role and consideration for our clients and employees. Today, we are in a position to promote our values across five continents and numerous industries. This new firm, an expert in transformation, is decisively entrepreneurial and is the right size to position itself beyond the role of a simple consultant to be considered more as a trusting advisor, passionate about our clients’ businesses,” affirms Chiheb Mahjoub, president and CEO of Kurt Salmon. In characterizing the new firm Mark Wietecha, Chairman, states: “In merging, we have recognized our need for larger global scale and investment capability to better serve our clients. At the same time, our unique proposition continues to be one of industry specialization. Our large and vertically organized industry practices in the consumer and retail sector and in the financial services sector are clear global leaders in bringing our clients dedicated specialty services. The concept of industry specialization continues to be one of our most unique competitive advantages, and one we aim to extend into those sectors requiring globally organized consulting.” “The new Kurt Salmon combines Ineums geographic footprint and functional expertise with Kurt Salmon Associates domain expertise. We now have a more powerful message to communicate to the US and global marketplace and an increased ability to deliver great services to great clients, said John Karonis, Managing Director of Kurt Salmon, United States. Kurt Salmon operates in offices throughout the world including Algeria, Australia, Belgium, France, Germany, Hong Kong, Italy, Japan, Luxembourg, Morocco, Shanghai, Switzerland, Tunisia, United Kingdom and the United States. Kurt Salmon’s clients have access to specialized teams across all major markets, either by industry (retail and consumer products, financial services, communication and media, healthcare, energy and utilities), or by functional competency (operations management, CIO advisory, strategy/transactions, financial management, etc.). About Kurt Salmon Kurt Salmon Associates and Ineum Consulting have joined forces to create an integrated and global organization, operating across five continents under one single brand: Kurt Salmon. Our clients draw from the deep industry and functional experience of our 1,600 consultants in strategy, organization and management. Todays increasingly complex environment demands more than just a consultant—as a trusted advisor, Kurt Salmon works with you to design and then drive strategies and solutions that make a lasting and meaningful impact. Kurt Salmon is committed to delivering measurable results for its clients through executional excellence. Kurt Salmon is a company of Management Consulting Group (MMC - London Stock Exchange). Learn more at: www.kurtsalmon.com Published Jan. 13, 2011 Copyright © 2011 SYS-CON Media, Inc. — All Rights Reserved. Syndicated stories and blog feeds, all rights reserved by the author. About Business Wire Copyright © 2009 Business Wire. All rights reserved. Republication or redistribution of Business Wire content is expressly prohibited without the prior written consent of Business Wire. Business Wire shall not be liable for any errors or delays in the content, or for any actions taken in reliance thereon. Subscribe to the Worlds Most Powerful Newsletters Subscribe to Our Rss Feeds  Get Your SYS-CON News Live! Click to Add our RSS Feeds to the Service of Your Choice: View Additional SYS-CON Feeds Publish Your Article! Please send it to editorial(at)sys-con.com! Advertise on this site! Contact advertising(at)sys-con.com! 201 802-3021  SYS-CON Featured Whitepapers ADS BY GOOGLE  Breaking Java News ATW Gold Corp.: Name Change to Redhill Resources Corp. OnStar Looking for Application Developers of the Future C7 Technologies and Dalcon Communication Systems, Inc. Announce Partnership TeamStaff, Inc. Announces Delay of Year End Results Billionaire Alki David and Mike Mozart Release Second Incendiary CBS Video in Response to Leslie Moonves Comments American Capital Agency Corp. Announces Pricing of Public Offering of Common Stock The X-Change Corporation Completes the 2010 Audit and Files a 10k to Complete the Asset Purchase of 21-Century Silicon, Inc. LSSOs Legal Lean Sigma(TM) Process Improvement Certifications Help Legal Profession Increase Efficiency, Deliver Value and Boost Profits Seattle Lighting Receives First Batch of VU1 ESL Energy Efficient Light Bulbs INOVA Announces Sale to One of the Largest Operating Crews in Southern Iraq  ADVERTISE   |   MAGAZINE SUBSCRIPTIONS   |   FREE BREAKING-NEWSLETTERS!   |   SYS-CON.TV   |   BLOG-N-PLAY!   |   WEBCAST   |   EDUCATION   |   RESEARCH .NET Developers Journal - .NETDJ   |   ColdFusion Developers Journal - CFDJ   |   Eclipse Developers Journal - EDJ   |   Enterprise Open Source Magazine - EOS Open Web Developers Journal - OPENWEB   |   iPhone Developers Journal - iPHONE   |   Virtualization - Virtualization   |   Java Developers Journal - JDJ   |   Linux.SYS-CON.com PowerBuilder Developers Journal - PBDJ   |   SEO / SEM Journal - SJ   |   SOAWorld Magazine - SOAWM   |   IT Solutions Guide - ITSG   |   Symbian Developers Journal - SDJ WebLogic Developers Journal - WLDJ   |   WebSphere Journal - WJ   |   Wireless Business  Technology - WBT   |   XML-Journal - XMLJ   |   Internet Video - iTV Flex Developers Journal - Flex   |   AJAXWorld Magazine - AWM   |   Silverlight Developers Journal - SLDJ   |   PHP.SYS-CON.com   |   Web 2.0 Journal - WEB2 Apache   |   CMS   |   CRM   |   HP   |   Oracle Journal   |   Perl   |   Python   |   Red Hat   |   Ruby on Rails   |   SAP   |   SaaS SYS-CON MEDIA:   ABOUT US   |   CONTACT US   |   COMPANY NEWS   |   CAREERS   |   SITE MAP SYS-CON EVENTS:   |  AJAXWorld Conference  Expo  |  iPhone Developer Summit  |  Cloud Computing Conference  Expo  |  SOA World Conference  Expo  |  Virtualization Conference  Expo INTERNATIONAL SITES:   India  |  U.K.  |  Canada  |  Germany  |  France  |  Australia  |  Italy  |  Spain  |  Netherlands  |  Brazil  |  Belgium  Terms of Use  Our Privacy Statement     About Newsfeeds / Video Feeds Copyright ©1994-2008 SYS-CON Publications, Inc. All Rights Reserved. All marks are trademarks of SYS-CON Media. Reproduction in whole or in part in any form or medium without express written permission of SYS-CON Publications, Inc. is prohibited.    close this window