<root><blog><title>Purdue Boilermakers @ Minnesota Golden Gophers GameThread, Jan 13, 2011 6:00 PM CST - The Daily Gopher</title><content>Purdue Boilermakers @ Minnesota Golden Gophers GameThread, Jan 13, 2011 6:00 PM CST - The Daily Gopher The Daily Gopher: An SB Nation Community Navigation: Jump to content areas: Network Bar  Login Section Navigation Main Blog Content Secondary Sidebar: Links to Recent Stories, FanPosts and FanShots Masthead Network Bar SB Nation Pro Quality. Fan Perspective. Log In Screen Name Password Remember Forgot Password? Sign in with Yahoo! ID Sign in with Facebook Use OpenID OpenID Remember Dont Have OpenID? Sign Up The Daily Gopher - Your online home for Minnesota Golden Gophers football, basketball and hockey. Home FanPosts FanShots Archives Golden Gophers Schedule Roster Stats Explore all 296 Sports Blogs » The Gophers Return Home to Hose the Purdue Boilermakers - OPEN THREAD by GopherNation on Jan 13, 2011 4:30 PM CST in Gopher Basketball Tweet 0 comments Email Print Purdue Boilermakers at Minnesota Golden Gophers, Jan 13, 2011 6:00 PM CST Well at least the road brutality has ended but things dont really get any easier at home as we are set to face the best defensive team in the Big Ten and they have a few strong offensive weapons as well.  We all know that this team lost a potential All-American in Robbie Hummell but they have a couple first team All-Big Ten caliber players in Moore and Johnson so this team is not without talent. Game Time: 6:00 CST TV: ESPN   Pos #25 - Minnesota Pnt/Gm   Pnt/Gm #8 - Purdue Pos PG Al Nolen 8.4   5.6 Lewis Jackson G G Blake Hoffarber 13.4   18.8 E`Twaun Moore G F Rodney Williams 6.7   7.4 Ryne Smith F F Colton Iverson 6.3   5.2 D.J. Byrd F C Ralph Sampson III 10.7   19.4 JaJuan Johnson C Bench Trevor Mbakwe 13.5   5.9 Kelsey Barlow Bench Bench Austin Hollins 3.4   5.8 Terone Johnson Bench Bench Maverick Ahanmisi 2.1   1.5 Travis Carroll Bench   To be honest, I like a few of the match-ups above. Nolen vs. Jackson - good match-up of defensive minded point guards.  Both are playing well as of late but I dont look at this match-up and automatically put it in Purdues favor. Hoffarber vs. Moore - OK, this one Ill give to Purdue, Moore is very good.  In the three games last year Hoffarber scored 11 points...total...in three games.  Williams vs. Smith - not a slam dunk but the way Williams is playing lately I might even give the nod to Rodney.  Iverson/Mbakwe vs. Byrd - This is where the Gophers can make up some ground.  In the three games last year whoever was playing PF minutes really fared well against the Boilermakers.  Paul Carter had 15 off the bench in game 1, Damian Johnson scored a dozen in game 2 and game 3 doesnt really count cause the 27 point win was weird.  But Mbakwe could have a monster night tonight. Sampson vs. Johnson - should be a lock for Purdue right?  Except for that Ralph seems to show some fire and spark when facing Johnson.  RSIII didnt play in game 1 last year but game 2 was probably his most impressive in a Gopher uniform and game 3 was a 13 point performance.  Yes, Johnson is a potential All-American but look for Ralph to play some inspired ball tonight (PLEASE?). Purdue is the more talented team but so many times it is all about match-ups and compared to the other top teams in the Big Ten we match-up best with Purdue (Ohio State might be our worst).   KenPom Efficiency Stats Minnesota (57) Purdue (4) Record 12-4 15-1 Pnt / Poss 1.103 1.143 (23) Def Pnt / Poss 0.938 0.819 (2) Off eFG% 50.8% 52.1% Def eFG% 46.5% 42.8% (13) Off Reb % 39.6% (12) 35.4% Def Reb % 68.5% 71.6% (35) TO % 20.6% (159) 17.0 (18)   Much like the OSU numbers, these numbers are equally as ugly, KenPom gives us a 21% chance of winning.  For us to win I think it comes down to 2 things. 1 - Do NOT turn the ball over - The Boilermaker half-court pressure defense is the best in the Big Ten and we have not been very good at being strong with the ball.  This will be no easy task, especially when Tubby subs in his line change.  Many of our turnovers are really just carelessness.  Mbakwe must have at least 3 per game on passes that he bobbles out of bounds.  And then the freshmen perimeter players need to be strong and confident with the ball.  2 - Mbakwe has to have a big night.  Im sure Matt Painter is telling his defense that they must really make Mbakwe uncomfortable every time he has the ball.  Im certain that Johnson or someone from the perimeter will be coming with added pressure all night.  He can take the physical nature of being doubled but can he hang on to the ball and make his free throws?  He needs to be productive and hopefully that will free up Sampson a little bit.  And hopefully that will then free up Hoffarber a little bit.  But Mbakwe is the one who can really put the Gophers on his back and carry them. Can we win it?  Yes we can.  Should be fun to watch both teams try and control this game.  Id love to see Tweet 0 comments  |  Add comment  |  0 recs  |  Do you like this story? More from The Daily Gopher Daily Nugs 1.11.2011 Jan 2011 by Buck Bravo - 17 comments Gophers Come Close, Fall 67-64 to Ohio State Jan 2011 by PJS - 20 comments Gophers Get First Big Ten Win Jan 2011 by PJS - 19 comments Badgers hold off Gophers to snap their Minnesota losing streak Dec 2010 by GopherNation - 28 comments Gophers final prep for Big Ten play is a win over South Dakota State Dec 2010 by GopherNation - 13 comments Gophers Slog Through Against Akron Dec 2010 by PJS - 16 comments Around SB Nation Tonights College Basketball Picks Jan 2011 from Searching for Billy Edelin - 1 comment Purdue Vs. Minnesota: Boilers Look To Remain Undefeated In Conference Play Jan 2011 from BT Powerhouse - 1 comment Know Thy Opponent: Minnesota Golden Gophers Jan 2011 from Hammer and Rails - 48 comments CHAOS! The Big10 in Flux Jan 2011 from Hammer and Rails - 38 comments Big Ten Tonight Is Way Out In the Water, Still Swimming Jan 2011 from Sippin On Purple - 0 comments Read More: Trevor Mbakwe (F - Minnesota), Al Nolen (G - Minnesota), Blake Hoffarber (G - Minnesota), Damian Johnson (F - Minnesota), JaJuan Johnson (F - Purdue), E`Twaun Moore (G - Purdue), Paul Carter (F - Ill.-Chicago), Colton Iverson (F - Minnesota), Ralph Sampson III (F - Minnesota), Lewis Jackson (G - Purdue), Ryne Smith (G - Purdue), Kelsey Barlow (G - Purdue), D.J. Byrd (G - Purdue), Maverick Ahanmisi (G - Minnesota), Austin Hollins (G - Minnesota), Terone Johnson (G - Purdue), Travis Carroll (F - Purdue), Minnesota Golden Gophers, Purdue Boilermakers, Purdue Boilermakers at Minnesota Golden Gophers, Jan 13, 2011 6:00 PM CST Sign in with your Yahoo! ID Add The Daily Gopher to My Yahoo! Comments Display: Expanded Collapsed Something to say? Choose one of these options to log in. » Sign in with your Yahoo! ID » Create a new SB Nation account » Already registered with SB Nation? Log in! ? Top of comments ? Top of page ? GameThreads ? The Daily Gopher ? SB Nation Secondary Sidebar Search User Tools in association with Minnesota Golden Gophers sports--Usually analytical, sometimes snarky. Start posting about the Golden Gophers The Daily Gopher on Facebook Follow @TheDailyGopher Subscribe to The Daily Gopher Stories Related FanPosts on The Daily Gopher Trevor Mbakwe nickname suggestion by GopherNation 14 days ago 13 comments Video: Gophers Presser After UNC Win by PJS about 1 month ago 0 comments Tubby Smith names likely starters for Tuesdays scrimmage by GopherNation 2 months ago 9 comments Huge recruiting weekend for Gophers by GopherNation 4 months ago 20 comments Related FanShots on The Daily Gopher Can Al Nolen save Minnesota? by PJS 21 days ago 10 comments Joseph, Nolen and Williams Updates by PJS about 1 month ago 3 comments Gopher basketball played yesterday too by GopherNation 4 months ago 1 comment FINALLY, resolution to the Trevor Mbakwe trial by GopherNation 5 months ago 6 comments Paul Carter transferring to UIC by GopherNation 8 months ago 1 comment Uh Oh...Al Nolen ruled academically ineligible by GopherNation 12 months ago 3 comments FanPosts Community blog posts and discussion. Recent FanPosts Which team sport requires the most athletic ability? by fanoverboard about 2 hours ago 3 comments Big Ten Bloggers Pickem 2010 Final Standings by GopherNation 1 day ago 5 comments SB Nation College Bowl Pick Em Recap by rebelfan1 1 day ago 0 comments Mbakwe arrested by COJOMAY 3 days ago 18 comments Does Size Matter??? by Narby 7 days ago 4 comments Golden Gopher highlights of 2010 - OPEN THREAD by GopherNation 14 days ago 6 comments Trevor Mbakwe nickname suggestion by GopherNation 14 days ago 13 comments Minnesota/Indiana Hoops? by DallasGopher 14 days ago 0 comments SB Nation College Bowl Pick Em December 18th Recap by rebelfan1 25 days ago 0 comments SB Nation College Bowl Pick Em by rebelfan1 28 days ago 0 comments + New FanPost All FanPosts  Recent Posts Gophers vs. Boilermakers...Is tonights game a must win? Bill Hancock puts the BS in BCS as he makes another defense of the BCS Minnesota Gopher Hockey: Next 5 Series Will Decide the Season Daily Nugs 1.11.2011 The Afternoon Nugz 1.10.11 Gophers Come Close, Fall 67-64 to Ohio State Gopher Hockey: Minnesota vs. USA U-18 Golden Nugz 1.7.11 Minnesota Gophers Hockey: Lets Talk Some Hockey, Eh! Golden Nugz - 1.6.11 NCAA Basketball -- FanHouse NCAA Basketball Power Rankings: Ohio State No. 1 A.D. (After Duke) Jacob Pullen Says He Wont Play in NIT In Small Mans College Game, Big Men Have San Diego State Unbeaten Florida State Cant Rest on Upset of Top-Ranked Duke SBNation.com Recent Stories NCAA Basketball Debrief: The Pittsburgh Panthers Are Doing It On ... Offense? +4 updates There Will Be A New College Basketball No. 1: Florida State Downs Duke 66-61 +2 updates No. 5 Pittsburgh Shuts Down No. 22 Georgetown 72-57 As Hoyas Continue Fade More from SBNation.com  Community Masthead Managers GopherNation Buck Bravo Editors PJS Jeffrick JG2112 JDMill Official Partner of Copyright © 2011 Sportsblogs, Inc. About Us Frequently Asked Questions Terms of Service Privacy Policy Disclosure Contact Us Certain photos copyright © 2011 by Associated Press or Getty Images. Any commercial use or distribution without the express written consent of Associated Press and Getty Images is strictly prohibited. OpenCalais - Powered by Thomson Reuters</content></blog></root>